Preliminary Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art archives department records, circa 1890-2007 COR0005.3.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Archivist files, Series 4
  - Project files, Series 4 subseries 3
    - 501(c)3 IRS Letter, 1989; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Institute of Museum Services National Award for Museum Service, 1996 September 25; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 42, Item 23)
    - Working Draft Historic Structures Report Corcoran Gallery of Art Washington DC, 1996 September; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Masons/Kiwanis, circa 1990s; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Curatorial Records Processing, 1994 October; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Archives: Processing Records, circa 1990s; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Camp Edit, circa 1990s; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - NEH Journals, 1999; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - NHPRC, 1996; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Self Study CSA, circa 1990s; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - The Twitch, circa 1990s; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Burn Baby Burn, circa 1990s; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Kineret Abramson, 1997 Summer; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Laura Jacobs, 1997 Summer; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Archives - Loan, circa 1990s; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Kaira Henrickson, 1997 Fall; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - David Finn, circa 1990s; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Jackie Exhibition, 2002; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - NEH: Journals, 1998; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Plaster Replicas in Boah Archives, circa 1990s; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - SWA/WWC, circa 1990s; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Archives, circa 1990s; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Forms, circa 1990s; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Museum Archives Manuel, circa 1990s; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Program Committee, 2004; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Chillum, circa 1990s; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Book Survey, 1991; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Cornerstone laying 100th anniversary ceremony, 1994; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Curator's Journal project - applicant files, 2002; Series 4 subseries 3 (Box 44, Folders 27-30)
  - Professional activity, 1990-2003; Series 4 subseries 4
    Includes committee records, correspondence, records and planning for regional conferences, and tour records of Corcoran Archives staff.
    - SAA Host Committee, 2001; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Oak Hill Cemetery, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - SAA Session, 1998 Fall; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Mount Vernon GIS Talk, 1997 November 12; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - SAA Program, 1995; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - COPAR, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - SAA Focus Group, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - MARAC Program Committee, 1995 Fall; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - SAA Public Information Committee, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - SAA Task Force, 1996; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - MARAC, 2001 Fall; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - MARAC: Meeting Coordinating Committee, 1999-2001; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Local Arrangements, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - ARLIS/NARC, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Smithsonian Grant Panel, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - NFP/DC, 1997; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Librarian Search, 1999-2000; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - MARAC Fall 1998, 1998 Fall; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Outreach Workshop (MARAC), 1996 Fall; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - MARAC Panel, 1997 Fall; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - TFIPS Session (MARAC), 1996 Fall; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - ARLIS DC/MD/VA, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Interns, 1998; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Small Museums Conference, 2003; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Committee List, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Minutes - Full Host Committee, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Minutes - Tours/Special, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Ways & Means, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - History of DC, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Registration/Logistics, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Gopher Publicity, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - Deadlines/Schedule, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 32)
    - Reception Site, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 34)
    - Archives II Tour, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 35)
    - ICA Meeting, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 36)
    - Transportation, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 37)
    - Our Other Lives, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 38)
    - Previous DC Meetings, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 4 subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Research papers, 1947-1996; Series 4 subseries 5
    Contains the file of theses and dissertations related to the history of the Corcoran Gallery of Art maintained by the Corcoran Archivist. Materials date from 1947-1996.
    - The Corcoran Gallery and Ernest Flagg: Classicism, Influence, and Architecture by Wendy Wiener, 1996 Spring; Series 4 subseries 5 (Box 45, Item 1)
    - A Study of a Group of Greek Terracottas in the Corcoran Museum at Washington, DC, Sister Mary Mercy McCarran, SHN, 1947 Summer; Series 4 subseries 5 (Box 45, Item 2)
    - Public Relations in the Arts: Case Studies, Elizabeth Teall Kaster, 1978; Series 4 subseries 5 (Box 45, Item 3)
    - The Washington Gallery of Modern Art: A Report of on the Research Conducted by Sue Scott (revised), 1991; Series 4 subseries 5 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Washington Gallery of Modern Art by Judy Richardson Markley, 1989; Series 4 subseries 5 (Box 45, Item 5)
    - William Douglas MacLeod: His Life, Curatorship, and Art by Candace Nielsen Von Salzen, BS, Simmons College, 1967 June; Series 4 subseries 5 (Box 45, Item 6-7)
  - Legacy collection descriptions, Series 4 subseries 6
    Contains legacy and outdated collection guides, inventories, and historical notes providing background for the Corcoran Archives.
    - Guide to the Corcoran Archives, 1985; Series 4 subseries 6 (Box 45, Binder 8)
      This is a guide published in 1985 as part of the NEH grant to process the corcoran archives. It has a wealth of history, but any box/folder information is outdated.
    - Photocopies of historical newspaper entries related to W.W. Corcoran, undated; Series 4 subseries 6 (Box 45, Binder 9-10)
    - RG 7: Building & Grounds records, undated; Series 4 subseries 6 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Audiovisual records inventories, undated; Series 4 subseries 6 (Box 45, Folders 12-14)
    - Education department records, undated; Series 4 subseries 6 (Box 46, Folders 1-2)
    - Building and grounds records, undated; Series 4 subseries 6 (Box 46, Folders 3-6)
    - WGMA records, Series 4 subseries 6 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Washington Gallery of Modern Art records, Series 4 subseries 6 (Box 46, Folders 8-9)
    - School records, undated; Series 4 subseries 6 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Eugen Weisz papers, undated; Series 4 subseries 6 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - CP Minnegerode personal papers, undated; Series 4 subseries 6 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Reference and research requests, 1990s; Series 4 subseries 7
    Contains correspondence and printed email correspondence regarding research and reference requests for information and photocopies within the Corcoran Archives, circa 1990s.
    - Reference requests, circa 1990s; Series 4 subseries 7 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Reference requests, circa 1990s; Series 4 subseries 7 (Box 47, Folders 1-2)
    - Inquiries, 1998 July 1-December 31; Series 4 subseries 7 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries, 1997 July 1-December 31; Series 4 subseries 7 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Inquiries, 1997 January 1-June 30; Series 4 subseries 7 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Inquiries, 1998 January 1-June 30; Series 4 subseries 7 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Inquiries, 1996 July 1-December 31; Series 4 subseries 7 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Inquiries, 1996 January 1-June 30; Series 4 subseries 7 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Personnel files, 1980s-1990s; Series 4 subseries 8
    Contains internship and hiring forms, correspondence, and general personnel files for the Corcoran Archives staff.
    Personnel files are closed to research. Please see the public service librarian for assisance.
    - Archives staff files, 1980s-1990s; Series 4 subseries 8 (Box 47, Folders 3-6)
  - Administrative records, Series 4 subseries 9
    - Carter Industries, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Central Safe & Locksmith, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Clark Correspondence, 1904; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Job Descriptions, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Records Management General, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Archives/Founding/Admin, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Treasury Department, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - 100 Research History, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Donor Files, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Registrar's Files, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Berg, Lisa, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Batt Bates & Company, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - "B" Misc. - Individual, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Listing, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Budgeting, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Budget, 1992; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Picnic, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - NHPRC Grant, 1981-1982; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Archives Grants (Operations), 1990-1991; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - NEH Grant, 1982-1984; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Archives, 1984-1985; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Archives - General NARS, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - SAA Conservation Grant, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Regulations for Use of Archives, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Biennals- History, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 51, Folder 44)
    - Press Releases: Archives Opening/Project, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Library/Archive Research Center, 1982; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Research Requests: Staff, 1990-1991; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Calender Copy, 1991; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Archives Exhibit & Fyler DC Bicentennial- DC's Fine Arts Community & Artists of Federal City, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Trustees of the Corcoran Archives Exhibition, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Patron of the Arts, 1984; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Exhibition Planning, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Anton Otto Fischer Exhibition, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - William Dunlap (Modern), undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Robert Henri's Circle Archival Exhibition/Final Text & Documents J. Jenkins, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Robert Henri Exhibition (Early Research Material), 1985; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Biennials, 1985 February 22-April 28; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Pennsylvania Landscape Painters, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - War Exhibitions II, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Exhibition Planning, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Chronology of Historic Events, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Report to the Director from the Archive Committee, 28979; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Misc. Scrapbooks/Volumes, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Administrative History/Chronology, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - The Washington Daily News- Stars, 1970 April-June; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Master List: Watercolors, Drawings, & Pastels for CGA Catalog, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Cafe Storage, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Deacquisition Information, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Location Indicator, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Karshan Prints Exhibitions, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Summary Inventory, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - Assorted Calendar and Corcoran Notes, 1970-1971; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Vertical Files, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - Corcoran Directors & Trustees, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 30)
    - Board of Trustees, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 31)
    - Old Directors Corress. Folders List, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 32)
    - Trustees Files, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 33)
    - Preliminary Record Survey, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 34)
    - Clark Correspondence, 1905; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 35)
    - Special Events Working Notes, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 52, Folder 36)
    - 45th Biennial, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Lenders/Checklist Mark Bennett: TV Sets, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Program/Misc. Mark Bennett: TV Sets, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - NEH Grant Journals, undated; Series 4 subseries 9 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Constance Stuart Larrabee collection files, Series 4 subseries 10
    Related Archival Materials
    Constance Stuart Larrabee collection finding aid
    - Miscellaneous items for review, undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - 9 vintage WWII prints, undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - S.A. War Paintings, Generals - Constance Stuart Larrabee On All Fronts (proofs), undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Vintage print - Italy, WWII Larrabee, undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Corcoran lists for exhibit, undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Publicity, letters, clippings, undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Constance Stuart Larrabee Corcoran press, 1984; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Exhibit and catalogue/ Corcoran, 1984; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Constance Stuart Larrabee Scholarship - Corcoran, 1995; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Corcoran, 1984; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Incidental Image Yale, undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Personalities, Non-Africa, undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Current pix to do - pending, undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Pix by Ford, 1987; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - King's Prevention Contract, 1987 June 1; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Hurd House, undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Brendan Gill, undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - KODASNAP prints envelope, undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - WWII Pretoria exhibitions SA Painter, undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Vintage WWII originals, 1945; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous prints/negatives, undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous negatives, undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Certificates and telegrams, undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - N. Gordimer, undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - K.P. Personal pix, 1970-1985; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Item for review, undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Box of prints: New Mexico and Grand Canyon, 1982, 1985; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Box 27)
    - Box of prints: Greece, 1960; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Box 28)
    - Box of prints: Mexico, 1963; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 54, Box 29)
    - Tribal Photographs - negatives of installation, undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Tribal Photographs - installation pics, undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Jeep Trek newspaper clippings, undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Constance Stuart Larrabee correspondence, 1945 June 10; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - WWII Libertas items mounted on board, circa 1945; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Le Reve mounted on board, undated; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Letters attached to boards, 1940s; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - BBC studios correspondence, 1944 October 21; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - WWII permits mounted on board, 1944; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - US Army Headquarters travel orders mounted on board, 1944 October; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - South Africa route forms mounted on board, 1944; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - WWII newspaper clippings and map mounted on board, 1940s; Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - C. S. Larrabee Gift to CGA, Circa 2001; COR0005.3 Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 138, Folder 1)
      Administrative materials related to the donation from Constance Stuart Larrabee to the Corcoran Gallery of Art.
    - Larrabee: non-perm-coll loans, Circa 1998; COR0005.3 Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 138, Folder 2)
      AAdditional materials located by the Trustees of the Corcoran Gallery of Art and delivered to GW April 2022. Accession 2022.025
    - CSL archival materials process list, Circa 2000-2001; COR0005.3 Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Constance Larrabee, Circa 1997-1998; COR0005.3 Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Larrabee, Circa 1998; COR0005.3 Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Larrabee, Circa 1997-1998; COR0005.3 Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Larrabee, Constance Stuart Archival Materials on loan, Circa 1998; COR0005.3 Series 4 subseries 10 (Box 138, Folder 7)
- Publications, Series 5
  - Harlem Renaissance: A Brief Chronology, undated; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Paintings in the Grand Salon & Octagon Room of the Renwick Gallery lent by the Corcoran Gallery of Art, undated; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Vienna School of Fantastic Realism, undated; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Important American Painters & Sculptor Not Adequately Represented in the Collection of the Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1954; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - The Corcoran Gallery of Art: Biennial Report of the Women's Committee, 1968-1970; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Illustrated Handbook of Painting & Sculptures - the Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1926; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - American Paintings the Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1947; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - The Corcoran: The 7th Annual Area Exhibition, 1952-1953; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - The Corcoran Gallery of Art Bulletin: Vol 11, No. 4, 1961 December; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - The Corcoran Gallery of Art Bulletin: Vol. 2, No. 3, 1949 May; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - The Corcoran Gallery of Art Bulletin: Vol. 5, No. 2, 1952 February; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Dutch & Flemish Paintings- W.A. Clark Collection- Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1955; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - The Corcoran - the 12th Annual Area Exhibition, 1957-1958; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - The Corcoran - 13th Annual Area Exhibition Jury Action Notice, 1958; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - The Corcoran - 14th Annual Area Exhibition, 1959; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - The Corcoran - 16th Annual Area Exhibition, 1963; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Prospectus - the 26th Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting, 1959; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - The 27th Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting - Catalogue/Frame Forms, 1961; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Prospectus - the 28th Biennial of Contemporary American Painting, 1963; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Corcoran Ball, 1994; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Edward Weston, undated; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - The Art Show: Work from the 1960s by Edward Kienholz- Washington Gallery of Modern Art, Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - The Corcoran - Volume 1, Issue 4, 1992 March/April; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 23)
  - The Corcoran - Volume 2, Issue 2, 1992 November/December; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - The Corcoran - Volume 1, Issue 3, 1992 January/February; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 25)
  - The Corcoran Gallery of Art Public Programs Calendar, 1998 July; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - Corcoran Calendar, 1998 April; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 27)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art Public Programs Calendar, 1998; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 28)
  - The Corcoran - Volume 4, Issue 2, 1994 November/December; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 29)
  - The Corcoran - Night & Day, 1996 July/August; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 30)
  - The Corcoran - Night & Day, 1996 November/December; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - The Corcoran - Night & Day, 1995 July/August; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 32)
  - The Corcoran - Night & Day, 1995 March/April; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 33)
  - The Corcoran - Volume 2, Issue 6, 1993 July/August; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 34)
  - The Corcoran - Volume 2, Issue 3, 1993 January/February; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 35)
  - The Corcoran - Volume 2, Issue 4, 1993 March/April; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 36)
  - Prints of photographs relating to Songs of My People Exhibition - New African Visions, 1992; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 37)
  - Fuji News - Fuji and its Products Support 'Sea to Shining Sea', 1992; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 38)
  - Dai Nippon Printing- From Sea to Shining Sea A Portrait of America Photographs by Hiroji Kubota, 1992; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 39)
  - Mobil - Sponsored Museum Exhibitions, 1975-1991; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 40)
  - Parameters Concernings the Use of Photographs by Hiroji Kubota, 1992; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 41)
  - From Sea to Shining Sea A Portrait of America Photographs by Hiroji Kubota- Exhibition Biography, 1992; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 42)
  - Discovering Ellis Ruley - Exhibition Information, 1995; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 43)